myjibo.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy - Jibo

Your privacy is important to Jibo. So we've developed a Privacy Statement that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your personal information. Please let us know if you have any questions.

This Privacy Statement applies to Jibo, Inc. and any affiliated companies, and to the websites available under the domain [ www.jibo.com ](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.jibo.com&sa=D&ust=1476996909959000&usg=AFQjCNHLRoVD8aIQhP3_eUyqn7fVK4jg4w) (together, the “Site”).

This Privacy Statement relates to Jibo, Inc., or any subsidiary or affiliate (“Jibo”) and the use of Jibo® Products. Products include Jibo-branded technology products (the “Hardware,” including, without limitation, the Jibo Robot), related software and documentation (together, the “Software,” including, without limitation, the Jibo App, and any updates or upgrades), and various Jibo-related services (the “Services,” including, without limitation, cloud storage). This Agreement also applies, as applicable to the Site. Together, the Hardware, Software, Services, and Site are referred to herein as the “Products,” and each, a “Product.” For the avoidance of doubt, this Statement does not apply to third party Skills purchased on the Jibo Store that were not developed by Jibo.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact an individual person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information any time you are in contact with Jibo. Jibo and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and they may use it consistently with this Privacy Statement. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our Products, services, and content. You are not required to provide the personal information that we request, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our Products or respond to any queries you may have.

##### What Personal Information We Collect

Here are some examples of the types of personal information Jibo may collect and how we may use it:

  * When you create a Jibo Account, purchase a Product, download a software update, contact us or participate in an online survey, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, IP address, and credit card information.
  * When using Jibo Products, we may collect recordings of your voice or image, or other biometric identifiers.
  * When you share your content with family and friends using Jibo Products, send gift certificates and products, or invite others to participate in Jibo services or forums, Jibo may collect the information you provide about those people such as name, mailing address, email address, and phone number. Jibo will use such information to fulfill your requests, provide the relevant Product or service, or for anti-fraud purposes.
  * In the U.S., we may ask for a government issued ID in limited circumstances including when activating your device or as required by law.

##### How We Use Your Personal Information

  * The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Jibo's latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. If you don't want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out any time by updating your preferences or by clicking on the applicable unsubscribe buttons in each email.
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with Jibo, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.
  * We also use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, marketing, and for loss prevention and anti-fraud purposes.
  * We may use your personal information, including date of birth, to verify identity, assist with identification of users, and to determine appropriate services. For example, we may use date of birth to determine the age of Jibo Account holders in order to comply with privacy regulations which apply to children.
  * We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Jibo's Products, services, and customer communications.
  * If you enter into a sweepstake, contest, or similar promotion we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.
  * If we combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined and includes personal information.

##### Collection and Use of Additional Information

We also collect data in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, referrer URL, location, and the time zone where a Jibo Product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our Products and services.
  * We may collect information regarding customer activities on our website and Skill Store and from our other Products and services. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, Products, and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Statement.
  * We may collect and store details of how you use our services, including search queries. This information may be used to improve the relevancy of results provided by our services.
  * With your explicit consent, we may collect data about how you use your device and applications in order to help Skill developers improve their Skills.

#### Cookies and Other Technologies

Jibo's websites, online services, email messages, and advertisements may use "cookies" and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, and facilitate and measure the delivery of our services. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that IP addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information.

Jibo and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our website, online services, and Skills. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with Jibo more convenient and personal. For example, knowing your first name lets us welcome you the next time you visit the Skill Store. Knowing your country and language — and if you are an educator, your school — helps us provide a customized and more useful shopping experience. Knowing someone using your computer or device has shopped for a certain Product or used a particular service helps us make our email communications more relevant to your interests. And knowing your contact information, hardware identifiers, and information about your computer or device helps us personalize your operating system, set up your cloud-based services, as applicable, and provide you with better customer service.

If you want to disable cookies, most browsers will permit you to do so. Please note that certain features of the Jibo website will not be available once cookies are disabled.

We also gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit websites and applications, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, utterances, state change information, and metadata.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the services and Products, to learn about user behavior on the Jibo.com website, to improve our Product and services, and to gather aggregate demographic information about our user base as a whole.

In some of our email messages, we use a "click-through URL" linked to content on the Jibo website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.

#### Disclosure to Third Parties

##### Strategic Partners

At times Jibo may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with Jibo to provide Products and services, or that help Jibo market to customers. Personal information will only be shared by Jibo to provide or improve our Products, and services; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

##### Service Providers

Jibo shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering Products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our Products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever Jibo operates.

##### Others

It may be necessary — by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence — for Jibo to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.

#### Protection of Personal Information

Jibo takes the security of your personal information very seriously. Jibo online services such as the Skill Store protect your personal information during transit using encryption such as Transport Layer Security (TLS). When your personal data is stored by Jibo, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures. Your stored data (User Generated Content) is stored in encrypted form including when we utilize third party storage.

When you use some Jibo Products, services, or applications or post on a Jibo forum, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information and content you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to share or submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

If you or anyone else logs onto or uses a device that is owned by a third party, certain information shared within your Loop —including calendar, location, photos, and Skills purchases—may be downloaded on to that third party device thereby disclosing any such shared information.

#### Integrity and Retention of Personal Information

Jibo makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

#### Access to Personal Information

You can confirm that your contact information and preferences are up to date by logging in to your account through the site and the Skills. For other personal information we hold, we will provide you with a copy of such information upon your request. You may also request that we correct inaccurate data or delete data about you if Jibo is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made through by contacting Jibo (see Section 14, below).

#### Children

We understand the importance of taking extra precautions to protect the privacy and safety of children using Jibo Products and services. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from children under 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on jurisdiction, without first receiving verifiable parental consent we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

Children under the age of 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, are not permitted to create their own Jibo Accounts. With the affirmative permission of a parent or guardian, such children may be able to use Jibo Products in association with another’s Jibo Account, all pursuant to applicable procedures mandated by Jibo. If a parent needs to access, correct, or delete data associated with their or a child's usage in connection with a Jibo Account, they should contact Jibo (see Section 14, below).

#### Location-Based Services

To provide location-based services on Jibo Products, Jibo and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer, browser, or Jibo device. Where available, location-based services may use GPS, Bluetooth, and your IP address, along with crowd-sourced Wi-Fi hotspot and cell tower locations, and other technologies to determine your devices' approximate location. Unless you provide consent, this location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by Jibo and our partners and licensees to provide and improve location-based products and services. For example, your device may share its geographic location with application providers when you opt in to their location services.

Some location-based services offered by Jibo require your personal information for the feature to work.

#### Third-Party Sites and Services

Jibo websites, Products, applications, and services may contain links to third-party websites, Products, and services. Our Products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties — for example, a third-party Skill. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

#### International Users

All the information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world in support of our products and services as described in this Privacy Statement. In particular, Jibo uses servers and service providers located in the United States. If you do not want your personal information transferred to the United States, do not use the Products.

#### California Privacy Disclosures

##### Do Not Track

Jibo does not track its customers over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you.

##### Notice for Minors

Jibo may offer interactive services which allow you to post content to share publicly or with contacts. At any time you can delete or remove content you have posted using the deletion or removal options within our services. If you have questions about how to remove content you have posted, contact Jibo (see Section 14, below). Although we offer deletion capability for our services, you should be aware that the removal of content may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of that content or information posted through the services. For example, if your posted content has been copied and reposted by another user, you will not be able to remove such content.

#### Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy

To make sure your personal information is secure, we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to Jibo employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

#### Privacy Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about Jibo's Privacy Statement or data processing or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, please contact us. You can always contact us as set out below.

All such communications are examined and replies issued where appropriate as soon as possible. If you are unsatisfied with the reply received, you may refer your complaint to the relevant regulator in your jurisdiction. If you ask us, we will endeavor to provide you with information about relevant complaint avenues which may be applicable to your circumstances.

Jibo may update its Privacy Statement from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Statement.

##### Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our information practices, or your dealings with the Jibo website, please contact us:

Jibo, Inc.  
230 Congress Street  
Boston, MA 02110 USA  
Attn: Privacy
